https://www.allsafetyproducts.com/customer-and-website-privacy-security-policies.html

1-877-208-3109 (Toll Free in U.S.)
For manufacturer backorder status, please click on stock status link which lists products by category for updated stock / backorder status.  We will do our best to keep information updated on a daily basis.
Home
Product by Manufacturer
ASP Newsletter Signup
Sitemap
News
News Articles
Newsletters
Press Release
PCI Compliance / Customer Privacy
Financing - All Safety Products, Inc.
All Safety Products Policies
Export Terms and Conditions
Warranty and Shipping Info, Returns
Limited 1 Year Product Warranty for PJ Portable Handwash Sinks
3 Year Warranty for PolyJohn Portable Restrooms
Limited 5 Year Warranty for PP Portable Restrooms
Contact Us/Custom Quote
ASP Credit Application Form
Mail or Fax Order Form
Resources
Charitable Organizations / Community Outreach Info
God Provides Food Bank (CA Based)
International Justice Mission®
Restore and Rebuild Ministries
Ugandan Lambs Association USA
IMAGO WORK
ASP Products Catalogs
Helpful Tools / Charts for Customers
Restrooms and Sinks Event Planning Calculator
Glove Selection Chart - Chemical Breakthrough Time
Partners / Reciprocal Links
Alternate Suppliers Provided to All Safety Products, Inc.
Manufacturer Backorder Status
Contact Us
Ways to Contact Us
Contact Us/Custom Quote Form
Sales Commission Income Opportunity
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ)
About Us: All Safety Products
Shop by Manufacturer
My Account/Orders
My Account
View RFQ
Submit Quote
View Cart
Checkout
Ways to Contact Us
Portable Restrooms/ Portable Toilets
Portable Restrooms
ADA Compliant,
Wheelchair Accessible Portable Restrooms
GAP Compliant Portable Restrooms
Portable Restrooms for Disaster Relief and limited access locations
Waste Pump Out System
Portable Cold / Heated Showers
Portable Heated Showers
Portable Cold Showers
Ozark River
Portable Sinks
Ozark River Portable Sinks by Series
Ozark River Nature / Outdoor Portable Sinks
Ozark River Portable Sinks (Advantage Series)
Ozark River Portable Sinks (Education Series)
Ozark River Portable Sinks (Premier Series)
Ozark River Portable Sinks (Elite Series)
Ozark River Portable Sinks (Silver Series)
Ozark River Portable Sink Accessories
Portable Stainless
Steel Sinks
Portable Stainless Steel Sink Accessories
NSF Certified Portable Stainless Steel Sinks
NSF Certified Portable Stainless Steel Sink Accessories
Portable Hand Wash
Sinks / Sanitizers
Portable Hand Wash Sinks (By Type)
Portable Single User Hand Wash Sinks
Double Bowl Portable Hand Wash Sinks
Heated Portable Handwash Sinks
Four Bowl Portable Hand Wash Sinks
Portable Hand Wash Sink (Water Mains Hookup)
Vehicle / Wall Mount Hand Wash Sink (12v / 110v)
Portable Sink Accessories and Refill Items
Portable Hand Sanitizer Dispensers
PolyJohn Portable Sink Replacement Parts
Clearance/
Overstock
SAO™ Tersano™
Sanitizers - CA
Tersano i-Clean Mini SAO Dispenser - California Only
Tersano™ SAO™ Dispenser and Cartridges - California Only
Tersano SAO™ Additional Products and Accessories (California Only)
Industrial SafetyProducts / PPE
WEDJ Lab Pack Containers
RespiratoryProtection
FirstAid
HearingProtection
ProtectiveWorkwear
Head and FaceProtection
HandProtection
FallProtection
FacilitySafety
Veteran Owned Small Business (VOSB) • DUNS: 118927487 • CAGE CODE: 3BGW5
Home > Account Terms,Credit,Financing Options > All Safety Products PCI Compliance / Customer Privacy
All Safety Products PCI Compliance / Customer Privacy
Effective 09/2009 and Revised 01/2016PCI Compliance / Customer Privacy (Web Site Visitors)One can visit our Web site with complete privacy. A Web site visitor can choose to provide customer-specific information by ordering a product or service or corresponding with us through e-mail. Any information provided by a Web site visitor is held strictly confidential within our company and will not be sold to any other organization or business.Some Common Credit Card and Payment Processing Questions and Answers to Address Security Concerns about CIM and PCI Compliance:What does PCI stand for?The term PCI which stands for Payment Card Industry is frequently used in relation to both financial data security standards and also adding hardware to PC computers.  It has adopted PCI Compliance standardsHow private is my credit card information accessed by All Safety Products, Inc.? Only the last four numbers are visible to All Safety Products Accounting Staff or Authorize.net with all the rest of the credit numbers encrypted. This is encrypted using 128 bit SSL encryption to our secure gateway processor, Authorize.net, utilizing their CIM system. Does your website follow PCI compliance standards in keeping my confidential or company information and data secure?Yes, All Safety Products, Inc. places a high priority on keeping information confidential and private from others.  We also deal on a regular basis with government agencies (Federal, State, County and Municipal Agencies) who require a secure website.  Our website is audited regularly by through a PCI compliance auditing process by Elavon (PCI Compliance Manager). We have a Digicert SSL certificate for our website.  Our gateway processor, Authorize.net is secure and known throughout the internet Retail Commerce Industry as a reliable and secure Gateway Processor.  Our credit card payment link to our bank is handled by Elavon with a product called Converge.   How does All Safety Products use our credit card information if we choose to “Remember payment information…” option?We use it to adjust shipping charges or product prices only with your permission.  It is our company policy to charge actual freight charges only.  New orders are only placed with your permission or for your shopping convenience when you place a new order on our website, by e-mail, by fax or over the phone.  We review all orders before processing for accuracy. For any other privacy / security concerns, please contact our direct customer service line at 562-630-3700 or e-mail us at sales@allsafetyproducts.com .Types of Customer Information On some Web pages users can order products, make requests for certain information. Such customer-specific information will be used to fulfill the specific request or purpose for which it was provided. In addition, such voluntarily provided information may be occasionally used to offer products and services that may be of interest. Internet users have a choice to "opt out" if they prefer not to receive this type of information.Privacy of On-line Personal information No personal information obtained on-line is released outside of All Safety Products, except with the customer's permission, as required by law, for safety reasons, or to survey customer satisfaction, under nondisclosure protection. We use the information provided when placing an order to complete that order. We do not share that information with outside parties except as necessary to fulfill the on-line order (e.g., providing the "ship to" address to our shipper.) We may also use that information to offer other products or services of interest. We do not sell customer information to any outside party.Use of Customer Information Information collected on-line, especially from those who place an order on-line, may be used within All Safety Products to inform the user about services and products of potential interest. Customers might be contacted by telephone, direct mail or e-mail to keep them up-to-date on new products and services offered by All Safety Products. Web visitors or Internet service subscribers who do not want to hear about new products or services can opt out of any potential use of customer information with an opt out statement included in the body of the e-mail.Access by Children All Safety Products web site is not structured to attract children under the age of 16. We believe there is no information on our web site, which is inappropriate for viewing by children.Other Web Sites All Safety Products web site may contain links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of other sites.Data Security for Ordering Consumers are able to order safety products through our website with complete security in mind. Our host secure server software encrypts all of your personal information including credit card number, name, address, and order information, so that it cannot be read as it travels over the Internet.To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure only appropriate use of information, appropriate physical, electronic and managerial safeguards have been established through our host provider to secure the information collected on-line.Updates To improve the service of All Safety Products, the information obtained about Web users may be revised in the future. This privacy statement will be updated to reflect any future developments in Internet business practices.Changing Your Non-Public Personal InformationAll Safety Products provides you with the opportunity to change your non-public personal information online for all registration information. Please contact All Safety Products to change any non-public personal information provided to us through a contact form.If you have any questions or concerns about any privacy issues, please contact us at customerservice@allsafetyproducts.com or use our contact form.
Terms & Forms
PCI Compliance / Customer Privacy
Financing - All Safety Products, Inc.
All Safety Products Policies
Export Terms and Conditions
Warranty and Shipping Info, Returns
Limited 1 Year Product Warranty for PJ Portable Handwash Sinks
3 Year Warranty for PolyJohn Portable Restrooms
Limited 5 Year Warranty for PP Portable Restrooms
Contact Us/Custom Quote
ASP Credit Application Form
Mail or Fax Order Form
Resources
ALL SAFETY PRODUCTS -RIGHT PRICE, RIGHT CHOICE, RIGHT FOR YOU!
Proposition 65 for purchases in California
! WARNING: Products listed on website may contain chemicals known to the State of California to cause cancer and or/birth defects or other reproductive harm.  For more information go to www.P65Warnings.ca.gov
©2020 All Safety Products • Attn: Sales Dept. • P.O. Box 3822
Lakewood, California 90711-3822
Toll Free in U.S.: 1-877-208-3109 • Direct Customer Service: (562) 630-3700 • Fax: 1-562-630-3800
Portable Restrooms, Toilets, and Urinals Refill Items and Accessories
Cleaners, Deodorizers, Graffiti Removers
ADA Compliant,
Wheelchair Accessible Portable Restrooms
GAP Compliant Portable Restrooms
Portable Restrooms for Disaster Relief and limited access locations
Ozark River Portable Sinks (Advantage Series)
Ozark River Portable Sinks (Education Series)
Ozark River Portable Sinks (Premier Series)
Ozark River Portable Sinks (Elite Series)
Ozark River Portable Sinks (Silver Series)
Portable Hand Wash Sinks (By Type)
Portable Single User Hand Wash Sinks
Double Bowl Portable Hand Wash Sinks
Heated Portable Handwash Sinks
Four Bowl Portable Hand Wash Sinks
Portable Hand Wash Sink (Water Mains Hookup)
Vehicle / Wall Mount Hand Wash Sink (12v / 110v)
Dipped Gloves (PVC, Nitrile, Neoprene)
Emergency Lighting, Flashlights, etc.
Towels, Wipers,
Supplied Air Systems (complete)
Supplied Air System Pumps (oil-less)
Supplied Air Systems
Supplied Air Respirators
S.C.B.A. (Self Contained Breathing Apparatus)
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ)
About Us: All Safety Products
